<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<CLISH_MODULE xmlns="http://clish.sourceforge.net/XMLSchema" 
			  xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" 
			  xsi:schemaLocation="http://clish.sourceforge.net/XMLSchema
              http://clish.sourceforge.net/XMLSchema/clish.xsd">

    <!--===================================================-->
    <COMMAND name="show dot11"
                 help="Display 802.11 configuration">
    </COMMAND>
    <!--===================================================-->
    <COMMAND name="show dot11 accesspoint"
	     help="Display Access Point configuration.

This command displays the list of configured Access Points for the
device. From this summary list, status and parameters of each AP are
available for display.

<ap_name>: This is an AP identifier which uniquely identifies an AP in
the list of configured APs.

<Enabled>: An AP can be disabled if not in use and enabled as
needed. The AP is disabled if this field has the value 'N' and it is
enabled if it has the value 'Y'. Disabling an AP does not delete the
configuration, but stops the AP. Enabling the AP creates a wireless
network where computers and other devices can join and communicate
with the devices connected to the access point or the devices on the
Local Area Network (LAN).

<SSID>: The name or Service Set Identifier (SSID) is the name of the
wireless network serviced by this AP. Note that since a given wireless
profile can be common to multiple APs, the SSID is not unique to an
AP. In order for computers or devices to communicate via this wireless
network serviced by this AP, all devices must select the same SSID
from the list of wireless networks in the area.

<Broadcast>: The field indicates whether SSID is broadcasted or not in
the beacon frames transmitted by the AP. If SSID is not broadcast, the
wireless devices will not be able to see the network name (SSID). If
this field has the value 'Y', it indicates that the AP's SSID is
broadcasted to the public. If it is 'N' it indicates the SSID is not
to be broadcasted and a device would have to specify the SSID exactly
to connect to this AP.

<Profile>: This field has a brief description of the security,
encryption and authentication combination assigned to the AP. A
Profile is not necessarily unique to an AP, rather this grouping of
wireless settings can be used on more than one AP at the same time.

<Radio>: The physical radio(s) on which this AP is running on. An AP
can run on multiple radios at the same time for load-balancing and
better throughput.

<VLAN>: The AP can be part of a logical network defined by the VLAN id.
This allows devices connected to the VLAN through this AP to exchange
data with one another as in a LAN.

If the optional argument <ap_name> is specified, the following
configuration information is displayed for the access point.

<Beacon Interval>: The amount of time in milliseconds between beacon
transmissions.

<DTIM Interval>: Interval for delivery of traffic indication
message. It is related to beacon interval.

<RTS Threshold>: The Request to Send (RTS) threshold is the value the
AP checks against its transmitting frames to determine if the
RTS/Clear To Send (CTS) handshake is required with the receiving
client. Using a small value causes RTS packets to be sent more often,
consuming more of the available bandwidth, therefore reducing the
apparent throughput of the network packet. The default is 2346, which
effectively disables RTS.

<Frag Threshold>: This is the maximum length of the frame, beyond
which packets must be broken up (fragmented) into two or more
frames. Collisions occur more often for long frames because sending
them occupies the channel for a longer. The default is 2346, which
effectively disables Fragmentation.

<Preamble Mode>: 802.11b requires that a preamble be prepended to
every frame before it is transmitted to the air. The preamble may be
either the traditional long preamble, which requires 192 µs for
transmission, or it may be an optional short preamble that requires
only 96 µs. Long preamble is needed for the compatibility with legacy
802.11 systems operating at 1 and 2 Mbps. The default is 'long'.

<RTS/CTS Protection>: If selected the AP always performs RTS/CTS
handshake before transmitting a packet. It is generally used to
minimize collisions among hidden stations

<Transmit Power Gain>: Defines the relative amplification (gain) in
dbm for transmitted packets which is added to the TX power configured
on the physical radio.

<Retry Limit>: The number of retries the AP will use when a frame
transmission fails. It is used for both long and short frames, of size
less than or equal to the RTS threshold.

<Supported Rate>: The rate or rates (in Mbps) which the AP will
advertise in the beacon frames.

">
	     <PARAM name="ap_name" 
		    help="Name of the Access Point."
		    default="all"
		    ptype="STRING"/>
	     <ACTION>lua clishCmdExec(dot11APGet, "${ap_name}")
	     </ACTION>
    </COMMAND>
    <!--===================================================-->
    <COMMAND name="show dot11 profile"
	     help="Display Profile configuration. If no profile name
is specified, this command will display a summary of the details of
all the profiles configured in the system. If a profile name is
specified, this command will display a detailed configured of the
profile. If the argument 'DisplayQosInfo' is set to 'Y', the profile
details will include the QoS details as well.">
	     <PARAM name="profile_name" 
		    help="Name of the Profile"
		    default="all" 
		    ptype="STRING"/>
	     <PARAM name="display_qos" 
		    help="Display Quality of Service Information"
		    default="N"
		    ptype="CHOICE"/>
	     <ACTION>lua clishCmdExec (dot11ProfileGet, "${profile_name}",
			  "${display_qos}")
             </ACTION>
    </COMMAND>
    <!--===================================================-->
    <COMMAND name="show dot11 statistics"
	     help="Display access point and radio statistics.

This table shows a cumulative total of relevant wireless statistics
for the APs and radios; the counter is reset when the device is
rebooted.

Radio Statistics
This table displays transmit/receive data for each radio. It has the
following fields:

<Pkt(Tx/Rx)>: The number of transmitted/received wireless packets
<Byte(Tx/Rx)>: The number of transmitted/received bytes of information
<Err(TRx/Rx)>: The number of transmitted/received packet errors
reported to the radio
<Drop(Tx/Rx)>: The number of transmitted/received packet drops between
the radio and client
<Mcast>: The number of multicast packets sent over this radio
<Coll>: The number of packet collisions reported to the radio

AP Statistics
This table displays transmit/receive data for each AP. An AP can have
multiple entries if it is running on multiple radios. It has the
following fields:

<Pkt(Tx/Rx)>: The number of transmitted/received wireless packets
<Byte(Tx/Rx)>: The number of transmitted/received bytes of information
<Err(TRx/Rx)>: The number of transmitted/received packet errors reported to
the AP
<Drop(Tx/Rx)>: The number of transmitted/received packet dropped by the AP
<Mcast>: The number of multicast packets sent over this AP
<Coll>: The number of packet collisions reported to the AP

">
	     <ACTION>lua clishCmdExec (dot11accesspointallGet)
             </ACTION>
    </COMMAND>
    <!--===================================================-->
    <COMMAND name="show dot11 acl"
	     help="Display access control list information for the specified access point.">
	     <PARAM name="ap_name" 
		    help="Name of the access point."
		    ptype="STRING"/>
	     <ACTION>lua clishCmdExec (dot11ACLGet, "${ap_name}")
             </ACTION>
    </COMMAND>
    <!--===================================================-->
    <COMMAND name="show dot11 accesspoint status"
	     help="Display wireless stats.">
	     <PARAM name="ap_name" 
		    help="Name of the access point."
		    ptype="STRING"/>
	     <ACTION>lua clishCmdExec (dot11accesspointGet, "${ap_name}")
             </ACTION>
    </COMMAND>
    <COMMAND name="show dot11 wmm"
	     help="Display wireless stats.">
	     <PARAM name="profile_name" 
		    help="Name of the access point."
		    ptype="STRING"/>
	     <ACTION>lua clishCmdExec (dot11WmmProfileGet, "${profile_name}")
             </ACTION>
    </COMMAND>

    <!--===================================================-->
    <COMMAND name="show dot11 radius"
	     help="Display radius Information.">
	     <ACTION>lua clishCmdExec (dot11radiusGet)
             </ACTION>
    </COMMAND>
    <!--===================================================-->
    <COMMAND name="show dot11 wps"
	     help="Display WPS Information.">
	     <ACTION>lua clishCmdExec (dot11wpsGet)
             </ACTION>
    </COMMAND>
    <!--===================================================-->
    <COMMAND name="show dot11 wds"
	     help="Display WDS Information.">
	     <PARAM name="radio_no" 
		    help="Name of the access point."
		    ptype="UINT"/>
	     <ACTION>lua clishCmdExec (dot11wdsGet, "${radio_no}")
             </ACTION>
    </COMMAND>
    <!--===================================================-->
    <COMMAND name="show dot11 wireless_statistics"
	     help="Display wireless_statistics Information.">
	     <ACTION>lua clishCmdExec (dot11WirelessGet)
             </ACTION>
    </COMMAND>
  <!--===================================================-->

    <COMMAND name="show dot11 radio"
             help="Display Radio configuration

Available Radios
This table shows the list of available radios that an AP may use. It
has the following fields:

<Radio>: The radio number.

<Card>: This field indicates which card the radio is using.

<Path>: This field indicates which path the radio is mapped to.

<RogueAP Enabled>: If this field has value 'Y' it indicates that
RogueAP detection is enabled on this radio. If it is 'N' it indicates
that RogueAP detection is disabled on this radio.

If the optional argument <radioNum> is given the following
cofiguration information is displayed for the given radio.

Radio Settings
<Radio>: The radio number.

<Card Name>: This field indicates which card the radio is using.

<Path>: This field indicates which path the radio is mapped to.

<Current Channel>: The channel used by the radio.

<RogueAP Enabled>: If this field has the value 'Yes' it indicates that
RogueAP detection is enabled on this radio.

<TX Power>: Value in dBm is the default transmitted power level for
all APs that use this radio.

<RX Diversity: Enable receive diversity (use multiple antennas to receive packets)

List of Access Points for Radio
This table shows all the APs that are configured for a particular
radio.

<AP Name>: This is the name of the AP.

<BSSID>: The BSSID of the AP

<SSID>: The SSID serviced by AP

<Profile>: This field has a brief description of the security,
encryption and authentication combination assigned to the AP. 

">
    	     <PARAM name="radio_no" 
		    help="Radio number."
		    ptype="UINT"/>

	     <ACTION>lua clishCmdExec (dot11RadioGet, "${radio_no}")
             </ACTION>
    </COMMAND>
</CLISH_MODULE>
